<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>A Hugo website</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on A Hugo website</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>My First Tidy Tuesday: Taylor Swift</title>
      <link>/2020/10/10/tidy-taylor-tuesday/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 10 Oct 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/10/10/tidy-taylor-tuesday/</guid>
      <description>There’s not a lot of things I would consider myself an expert in — definitely not an expert in ggplot or making graphs. But, I am 100% confident in declaring myself an expert in all things Taylor Swift.
Thus, it’s only fitting that my very first Tidy Tuesday project is about Taylor Swift lyrics. This data comes from Rosie Baillie and Dr. Sara Stoudt. I was inspired by Rosie’s original post (the bulk of my code is from her), where she analyzed sentiments and emotions for the songs and albums.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Financial situation is greatest obstacle faced by Canadian students</title>
      <link>/2020/09/25/financial-situation-is-greatest-obstacle/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 25 Sep 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2020/09/25/financial-situation-is-greatest-obstacle/</guid>
      <description>Abstract Many Canadian students have aspirations for higher levels of education, but do not always believe that it is likely to achieve them. This research studied the obstacles they face in obtaining their desired level of education as reported in the 2016 General Social Survey conducted by Statistics Canada. It found that financial situation was the most common obstacle and women were more likely to face obstacles. These findings reiterate the existence of roadblocks in attaining education and the importance for government funding and financial aid to make education accessible for all students.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 05 May 2016 21:48:51 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>This is a &amp;ldquo;hello world&amp;rdquo; example website for the blogdown package. The theme was forked from @jrutheiser/hugo-lithium-theme and modified by Yihui Xie.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
